https://www.oceanlakes.com/privacy-policy/#cookies

Search for:
MenuBook NowLodgingCampsitesFree Campsite FeaturesCampsite CableTVPull Through SitesConcrete Pads CloseVacation RentalsExpress Check-InAnnual Lease Sales CloseAmenitiesSandy Harbor Family Fun CenterGamesMini GolfPoolsSplash ZoneCaféSnack Shak CloseCamptown CenterSandy MartSoapy SudsFluff n foldSandy’s Meet n EatCenter StageFree Wireless ZoneBrick Pavers CloseNature CenterOcean Lakes RV CenterChurchPrestwick GolfOutdoor FunShuffleboardFishingPing PongHorseshoesBasketballBocce BallVolleyballSkate Board CloseBicycle RentalsHandicap AccessRecreation Building CloseServicesOcean Lakes RV CenterCamper StorageGolf Car Sales &
RentalsProperty Sales & RentalsRallies
& GroupsLP GasInternet AccessPizza DeliveryEV Charging Station CloseThings to doActivity CalendarDo at HomePrestwick GolfBeach N’ BoogieBluegrass WeekendKamp StarfishCraft FairHalloweekendPolar Bear CloseRatesCampsite RatesCamper Storage RatesGolf Car Sales &
RentalsGift CertificatesDiscounts CloseAbout UsCoronavirus COVID-19FAQsMagazineStorm InfoBeach RenourishmentSwim AdvisoriesPoliciesParking Policies and OptionsBeach Laws and TentsCampsite PoliciesMotorcycle PoliciesGolf Car Policies CloseEmploymentMapsVirtual TourPhoto GalleryPress RoomiCare ProgramContact Us CloseQuick LinksContact UsDownload AppsSee & TourMagazineWeb CamsMapsForms/RegistrationEV Charging StationRules & PoliciesLocal AttractionsTravel PlanningGift CertificatesBuy Plush SandyJoin Our Enews Close
You are here:
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Ocean Lakes Family Campground, L.P. (“Ocean Lakes”) is committed to respecting the privacy of users. This Privacy Policy is the terms and conditions that apply to the online collection of data through our web sites (the “Site”).
This website may contain links to third party sites. We have no control over such third party sites and are not responsible for the privacy policies, actions or omissions of such third parties.
Collection and Use of Information
When you visit our Site, you do so anonymously unless you specifically choose to provide us with information that identifies you personally, for example through emails or making reservations. If you do provide us personally identifiable information, that information will be protected by security measures designed to preserve the confidentiality and security of your transactions.
We may request that you provide personal identifying information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, social security number, contact information, and other such information. We may also collect information about your use of our Site, such as what pages are being viewed and what features, services or offerings you use. We may collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, NIC address, browser type, domain names, access times and viewed Web sites and pages.
We may also inquire into preferential and/or life style information about you, but may not require such information to be provided. If you do provide such information, you consent to our use of this information. On use that we have of this information is to determine your potential desire to receive communications about particular products or services.
When you send us an email, we use your email address to reply, and for a limited time we may store your email address, your message, and our response for quality assurance purposes. We may also do this to meet legal and regulatory requirements.
We often use email to inform customers about products and services that we offer and that may be of interest after you. You will also have the opportunity to opt out of future messages with each marketing email you receive from Ocean Lakes. If you wish to opt out of receiving future emails, please follow the instructions at the bottom of emails that are sent to you to elect this option.
Our Use of Your Information
We use the information gathered on our Site to improve our services, and to generally try to provide a positive user experience. We may use your contact information in order to send you communications regarding updates to our Site, facilities programs or events, to survey your opinion of current features and services, or to try to determine potentially new products and services. Any feedback submitted by you becomes the property of Ocean Lakes, and we can use such feedback for marketing purposes or to contact you for further information.
Choices Regarding the Disclosure of Personal Information to Others
We do not disclose your personal information to third parties, or combined personal and demographic information or information about your use except as stated below:
1. If we have your consent.
2. We disclose information to companies and individuals we employ or contract with to perform administrative and operational functions. Such individuals and companies may provide goods and services such as web hosting, servers, metrics, marketing assistance, processing payments, reservations and customer service.
3. If legally required to do so, such as if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
4. If someone acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets whether voluntarily, bankruptcy proceeding, or receivership.
We may also share aggregated anonymous information about users with our clients to illustrate the type of users to our Site.
Use of Cookies
We may use “cookies” to enhance your use of our Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive by our web server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. When you return to our Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our Site.
Use of Web Beacons
Ocean Lakes pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. You may not decline web beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.
Security of the Personal Information
We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.
When you make reservations or purchase tickets or other items online at the Ocean Lakes Site, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. We use a service company to process its credit card transactions and see www.authorize.net for its security policies.
Children
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from children under 13 years of age; and that we obtain the consent of parents and guardians in order for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of our Site. Below we explain how we do that for these “kids.” Also, when we use the term “parent” below, we mean to include legal guardians.
Kids can use the Ocean Lakes Site to view content and play games without any personal information being collected.
Internet Safety
The best way to know what kids are doing online is to ask. Asking questions helps inform you what your kid is doing on the Internet so that you can insure they are making safe choices. Important information to try to gather includes: (a) What sites are visited; (b) What activates are conducted at each site; (c) Why do you go to that site; (d) How much time is spent on each site; (e) Did the kid have to register to use the site (e.g. provide personal information); (e) What information was requested; and (f) What information was given.
Following are basic safety rules for kids. However, there is no substitute for proper parental supervision, education and communications.
(a) Never share User ID, User Names or passwords;
(b) Don’t reveal any personal identity information (e.g. don’t include your name in your user name);
(c) Never give any personal information about yourself or someone else when communicating online such as in blogs or chat rooms;
(d) Don’t share photos of yourself, your family, or your home with people you meet online;
(e) Delete emails from strangers without opening them;
(f) If you receive mean, disrespectful or threatening comments from online users, immediately log off and tell your parents;
(g) Understand that there is rarely anything on the Internet that is completely private;
(h) Never make plans to meet an online “friend” in person.
Changes to Privacy Statement
If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policies, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.
Contact Information
privacy@oceanlakes.com
Ocean Lakes Family Campground
6001 South Kings Highway • Myrtle Beach, SC 29575
Main Office: 1-843-238-5636
Receive our latest offers, stories & event news, direct to your inbox
Rate This Park!
